

Denitsa Aleksandrova Asova

Nationality: Bulgarian Date of birth: 30/07/1999 Gender: Female

Carifornia Phone number: (+359) 882719664 **Email address:** deni.assova@gmailcom

■ Telegram: https://t.me/denitsa_assova

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/denitsa-assova-63070b23b/

Website: https://denitsaassova.github.io

• Home: Lozen, Yanko Panayotov Str. 42, 1151 Sofia (Germany)

ABOUT ME

At this point in my personal and professional development, I am a recent graduate holding a Master of Science in Informatics: Games Engineering from the Technical University of Munich. The time spent at this university, coupled with my five-year period as a student at the National Gymnasium of Mathematics and Natural Sciences in Bulgaria, has equipped me with valuable skills and proficiency in various programming languages (Java, C++, C#, Python, Assembly, etc.). Throughout my academic journey, I actively participated in various activities, taking on the role of the lead programmer for projects encompassing 3D modeling of spatial figures and single-player and multiplayer games. Additionally, I contributed as a member of the Math team at my gymnasium and served as a tutor at the university. These experiences not only shaped aspects of my character, such as perseverance and ambition, but also facilitated the improvement of skills related to teamwork, communication, and teaching.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Student with Academic Auxiliary Activities (Tutor)

Technical University of Munich [11/2022 - 02/2023]

City: Munich
Country: Germany

• Tutor for the Master's course "Patterns in Software Engineering"

- Supported students and the professor during the lecture and the in-lecture exercises
- Corrected homework exercises
- Corrected final exams

Student with academic auxiliary activities (Tutor)

Technical University of Munich [04/2021 – 07/2021]

City: Munich
Country: Germany

- Tutor for the Bachelor's course "Introduction to Software Engineering"
- Held two tutor groups per week, elaborating on the topics covered in the lecture
- Corrected homework exercises
- Corrected final exams

Student with academic auxiliary activities (Tutor)

Technical University of Munich [06/2020 - 09/2020]

City: Munich

Country: Germany

- Tutor for the Bachelor's course "Introduction to Software Engineering"
- Held two tutor groups per week, elaborating on the topics covered in the lecture
- Corrected homework exercises
- Corrected final exams

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Master of Science: Informatics: Games Engineering

Technical University of Munich [10/2021 - 11/2023]

Address: Arcisstraße 21, 80333 Munich (Germany)

Final grade: 1.7

Thesis: A VR Travel Application for Elderly People Focusing on Object Integration with Augmented Virtuality

Bachelor of Science: Informatics: Games Engineering

Technical University of Munich [10/2018 - 08/2021]

Address: Arcisstraße 21, 80333 Munich (Germany)

Final grade: 1.9

Thesis: An AR Serious Game about Obsessive-Compulsive Disorder

Online Course for Game Development

Awesome Tuts - https://www.awesometuts.com/ [06/2018 - 09/2018]

Secondary education

National High School of Mathematics and Natural Sciences "Academician Lyubomir Chakalov" [09/2013 – 05/2018]

Address: ul. "Bigla" 52, , 1164 Sofia, (Bulgaria) Field(s) of study: Mathematics and Informatics

Final grade: 5.97/6.00

Passed state matriculation exams:

- Mathematics 6.00/6.00 (23.05.2018)
- Bulgarian Language and Literature 5.81/6.00 (21.06.2018)

Elementary education

201 PS "St.St. Cyril and Methodius" [09/2006 – 08/2013]

Address: ul. "Sveti Sveti Kiril i Metodiy" 17, , 1151 Lozen, Sofia, (Bulgaria)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Bulgarian

Other language(s):

English German

LISTENING C2 READING C2 WRITING C2 LISTENING C2 READING C2 WRITING C2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION C2 SPOKEN INTERACTION C2 SPOKEN PRODUCTION C2 SPOKEN INTERACTION C2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

C, C++, C# / Java / Python / Assembly / Web Development: HTML 5, CSS, JavaScript / Unity 2D/3D / Unreal Engine / Visual Studio (Visual basic – C++, Visual InterDev) / Tools: Eclipse, IntelliJ, Maven, SVN, Git, LATEX

HONOURS AND AWARDS

Invitation for application for the Bavarian Elite Academy

[2020]

Invitation for application for the Bavarian Elite Academy

[2019]

Spring Mathematics Tournament - Third Team Place (Bulgaria)

[2017]

Invitation for the selection of the Bulgarian National Team for the European Girls' Mathematical Olympiad

[2016]

Autumn Mathematics Tournament - Third Team Place (Bulgaria)

[2016]

Invitation for the selection of the Bulgarian National Team for the European Girls' Mathematical Olympiad

[2015]

Mathematics Tournament "Chernorizets Hrabar" - First Place (Bulgaria)

[2013]

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Video games, Reading, Photography

Professional interests

My main professional focus revolves around serious game development, with a particular emphasis on exploring the utilization of Mixed Reality technologies in gaming, encompassing both Augmented and Virtual Reality, as well as Augmented Virtuality. Additionally, I am actively engaged in the domain of social gaming.

Link: https://denitsaassova.github.io

VOLUNTEERING

Annual Charity Bazaar "Traditions and Cuisine of the English speaking countries " (Avo Bell, Sofia)

[2014 - 2016]

SCHOLARSHIPS

"Boris Kamilarov" Scholarship

[2019]